Duh duh dun duh dun
Hmm
Duh duh dun chips and ketchup
Duh duh dun duh duh duh
Feeling a little bit sad today
Feeling a little bit bored
Brighton's waiting outside my door
But nothing sounds fun anymore
Could get a pizza at Donatello's
Sit in the lanes and watch the crowds go
But I'm not hungry so that's no good
Even though I know that the pizza would
There must be something
There must be somewhere
I've got the whole of Brighton
But I don't wanna go anywhere
Donatello's not hungry
The boldplex can't go straight
West Street to lefty
So where we going? Brighton Beach
So what shall we do? Where shall we be?
Let's just go down Brighton Beach
And draw dicks on pebbles
Get chips and ketchup for tea
Could go shopping in Churchill Square
But there were far too many people there
Queues at the tills and crowds downstairs
Could see a film at the marina
Big screen popcorn comfy seat
But the ticket price nearly made me cry
So I'll give that one a miss tonight
There must be something
There must be somewhere
I've got the whole of Brighton
But I don't wanna go anywhere
Donatello's not hungry
The boldplex can't go straight
West Street to lefty
So where we going? Brighton Beach
So what shall we do? Where shall we be?
Let's just go down Brighton Beach
And draw dicks on pebbles
Get chips and ketchup for tea
I could go bowling
But here's the thing
I aim for the middle and hit everything
Except for the pins that are straight ahead
The ball goes left and I turn bright red
I could go dancing down West Street
Neon lights and a 4-4 beat
But both of my feet wanna lead the way
And neither one knows how to dance anyway
So grab that sharpie, come with me
We'll make some art beside the sea
The goals can judge us
Let them be
We've got chips
And ketchup for tea
Donatello's not hungry
The boldplex can't go straight
West Street to lefty
So where we going? Brighton Beach
So what shall we do? Where shall we be?
Let's just go down Brighton Beach
And draw dicks on pebbles
Get chips and ketchup for tea
Draw dicks on pebbles
Down by the sea
You and me
Dicks on pebbles
And chips for tea
Let's just go down Brighton Beach
And draw dicks on pebbles
Get chips and ketchup for tea
Draw dicks on pebbles